What the fuck?
There she is.
How you feeling?
Like I was drugged.
Yeah.
There's a reason for that.
Come over here.
What is that?
It's a little pick-me-up.
Turn around.
Give me a cheek.
How long does it take to
What the fuck?
Bout that long...
Jesus.
You got another one to keep
my heart from exploding? Fuck!
You're welcome.
We're loading up.
How ya feelin' tiger?
I'm awake.
Good. Let's boogie.
I'm gonna break down her room.
I don't remember anything.
He drugged you. GHB we think.
We talked about this last night.
I don't remember.
Do I need to get
tested for STDs or something?
No need.
He didn't get that far.
How far did he get?
He didn't get nowhere.
We got there in time.
My underwear is gone.
We got there in the nick of time.
Marine. I wouldn't bullshit you on this.
Okay. Yeah.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Yeah. Don't got to ask me twice.
Fuck.
Neal. What do we know?
She's still in surgery.
Kaitlyn.
Hey. Neal.
You went gray.
When did that happen?
Last night.
Neal.
Alan.
Hey.
Hi. Jill.
So. she's in recovery.
The procedure went well.
There is considerable soft tissue damage.
but doesn't appear to
be significant nerve damage.
The procedure is called an
open reduction internal fixation
where we make an incision
that allows us to insert a rod
through the center of the femur.
and we attach a plate
outside to stabilize the fracture.
How long will it take to recover?
We have to look at healing
from three different perspectives.
The bone itself. the
soft tissue around the bone
and procedure site.
and the incision itself.
which is fairly substantial...
Just tell me what a
year from now is like for her.
Honestly. I don't know.
She's young. so that's an advantage.
but her bones are still growing.
So. how if at all does
this injury affect that growth?
Time answers that question.
Neal. can I talk to you for a second?
She's up to speed on everything.
Okay...
So she was spotting on the table.
so it looks like her
body rejected the pregnancy.
That's a decision we don't have to make.
When she wakes. I'll
get you back to recovery.
I want to be there when she wakes.
Okay. I'll bring you back.
Joe.
Can I have two hours?
Yeah. but you can't have three.
Coffee?
How's Errol?
He's happiest in a downturn.
Worse the economy. the jollier the man.
That's interesting.
What's the philosophy behind that?
Be greedy when everybody's scared
and scared when everybody's greedy.
Pretty good philosophy.
You can ask the
question you really want to ask.
Why bother. Kaitlyn?
You can't answer it.
If you need her in three hours today.
then you must really need her.
I do. Which is to say the nation does.
Which is why I'm not asking the question.
Don't give up on her. Neal.
I wish I could.
But when she walks in a
room it still takes my breath away.
Pretty good reason for sticking around.
Yep.
Hey.
Hey...
My friends are dead.
I know. honey.
I know how that feels.
And I hate that you know it now. too.
I'm so sorry.
I'm a bad mother.
I know that's what you think.
I'd think it too. if I
was in your shoes. I guess.
What you don't understand
is all the little moments of your life
that I've missed...
I missed those moments
so other families can have them.
It's you who makes the
sacrifice for the job I chose.
I always thought I was
setting an example for you.
that a woman can do virtually anything...
anything she sets her mind to.
And when I do my job well. lives are saved.
Just like your father.
he saves lives every day.
But he gets to come
home to you every night.
I envy him that.
Your mom's a soldier.
You can look at my life and you can choose
to live yours different.
I will respect that.
Fuck. I'll cheer that decision.
You can hate what I do. honey.
You can hate me.
But punishing yourself
is a terrible way to show it.
I don't hate you.
I just miss you.
I miss you. too.
Every day.
You're gonna be an adult soon enough.
and what you're dealing with right now.
these are adult problems.
Your whole life is going to
be nothing but adult problems
soon enough.
My advice to you?
Be a girl for as long as you can.
Don't rush to be a woman.
Cause once you are. you
don't ever get to be a girl again.
Did dad tell you everything?
Depends what you mean by everything.
Did he tell you about my... situation?
You mean your
situation of you getting pregnant?
What do I do?
God decided that.
What does that mean?
It means you're not pregnant anymore.
How does that make you feel?
I'm not ready to be a mother.
You know the one way to guarantee
you don't become one. right?
Look. the days of me
and your father grounding you
or inventing some punishment to keep you
from being exactly where you are right now?
Those days are gone.
We lost.
And life snuck up
and took a bite out of you.
And now I'm just here to...
just to give you advice.
Okay?
I've made all the mistakes you've made
and a lot more you
haven't thought about yet.
You got pregnant by accident?
Yeah.
What did you do?
My situation was a little different.
I was already married.
Your father was in
medical school. I was in a team.
Timing... Timing was terrible.
Did you get an abortion?
If I had. I wouldn't be
talking to you right now.
And so. every time I look at you
I think about that coat closet
at the Double Tree
Hotel that New Year's Eve.
Parents having sex for fun?
That is so gross.
Yeah.
Right back at ya. kiddo.
Do you know what's
going to happen to my leg?
I'm gonna leave the
doctor stuff to your father.
How you feeling?
Not feeling much.
They have a room ready for her.
We're going to take her up.
And I'll have an
orderly meet you in the lobby.
I've gotta go do something for work
and I'll be back in a few days. okay?
You won't be missing much.
Yes. I will.
Ma!
Hi.
They're taking her up to a room.
Yep.
I gotta go.
I gotta take care of something.
Yeah. I'm aware.
Few days type thing. or...
If I'm lucky.
When's the last time you were lucky?
Luck is perspective.
Only in your business.
You been good in school?
We're learning the alphabet in Russian.
Oh. in Russian?
Ah. beh. veh. yeow. byee...
I guess that's the
Fairfax County School Board
hedging a bet.
That's great. honey.
Making spies one first grader at a time.
I love you.
I'd say be careful.
but I know it's bad luck.
It's not that it's
bad luck. it's pointless.
Okay. see you soon.
Be careful.
She got ya there.
Yeah. I will.
Big hug. Bigger.
You didn't say it back.
I love you.
Call you when I can.
How'd it go?
Good.
She owned it.
Which is... good.
What about you?
I owned it too.
Sounds like a pretty good place to start.
What do you think
about becoming a station chief?
Then I'm gone all the time.
Somewhere you can take the family.
Somewhere like London.
They're still a target.
Well. you have to think of something.
Because my marriage
shouldn't be your goal. Joe...
In the meantime. let's see
if we can un-fuck this situation.
Your team is en route to Lackland.
We rendezvous there?
Gotta see the boss first.
These for us. right?
You the CAG team?
Don't know what that means.
Delta?
Never heard of 'em.
Whatever the fuck you guys call yourselves.
We go by nuthin'.
And neither do you.
Neither do you. 'sir'.
I'm a lieutenant.
I don't give a shit.
Which hangar is ours?
Seventeen.
They set up chow and cots?
It's squared away.
Hope you're talking about your food.
I don't want to get
in there and see a bunch
of fucking cold cuts.
Officers' catering is set up in the hangar.
You got couches. cable TV.
plywood walls on rollers.
looks like a cigar lounge now.
Good.
Where's my cigar. chief?
What?
Fucking mean "what?"
I lend you my team
and you fucking hang me.
Well. In case you haven't noticed.
I'm pretty fucking hung. too.
That sounds different
when I say it. doesn't it?
What I meant was I know what you meant.
Your intel better fucking be spot on
My intel is solid.
The house on the border is wired.
house in San Antonio's
got so many fucking cameras
we could shoot a God damn reality show.
That's what I'm fucking worried about.
Let's go.
Down here.
I want you close enough that if I yell
you can feel my fucking breath.
You ran an illegal operation on U.S. soil
that violates our rules of engagement.
U.S. Code 1385 that limits
our ability to operate on US soil.
You know. I've given
that a lot of thought. actually.
and USC 1385 relates specifically
to military being
deployed to enforce domestic policy.
Sorry. did you obtain a
law degree that I'm unaware of?
Actually. I did. I don't know if you know.
I have a degree in constitutional law.
If I may. Deputy Director...
Be my guest.
You keep giving answers to
question he hasn't even asked
so shut the fuck up.
When we want to hear you speak
we will tell you to fucking speak.
Yes. ma'am.
Thank you. Kaitlyn.
Fortunately for you. the intel is good.
It's actionable.
Joe. your team is on
standby in San Antonio.
You will have tactical
command. but Kyle is lead.
San Antonio SWAT will provide cover.
and they will take credit
if the mission is successful.
They will likely
arrest you if the mission fails
or somehow finds its way onto the streets.
Does your intel
indicate whether San Antonio
is a way station or target?
It appears to be a way station.
Our surveillance hasn't seen any footage
of IED materials or
weapons located on the premises.
Okay. this is not capture/kill.
This is capture only.
San Antonio SWAT can't explain
a half-dozen dead foreign nationals.
So you do it quiet. and you do it clean.
Have I made myself clear?
Yes. sir.
Kyle. you're dismissed.
The assets that I have
given you to complete your mission
are just that:
They are my assets that I allow you to use.
For missions that I approve.
I don't care if you witness a car jacking
in a church parking lot.
you do not deploy that
team without my permission.
Is that understood?
Yes. sir.
We owe a lot of
favors for this cowboy shit.
I don't care how good
the intel. ops are planned here.
Not on the back of a fucking napkin.
Understood. sir.
Go to San Antonio.
Why are you stopping?
I thought you wanted to talk.
We can talk on the plane.
Are you coming?
That's how much trouble you're in.
Bobby?
Yeah.
What the fuck is she doing here?
They sent us here.
They sent the team here.
That's not the team. that's the asset.
The asset.
Yeah. you think I'm
going to let you end up
on the news coming out of a safe house?
Or worse. eating a bullet inside it?
Bet I've kicked down
more doors than you have.
I highly doubt it.
A word. boss?
So. I was told there
was six targets in this house.
Correct.
Okay. well.
With you we're just six.
So. what. are we in the
business of fair fights now?
Come on. you know
this is a two squad minimum.
And I don't know
about you. but I don't feel like
rushing this place
with a fucking SWAT team.
It's not what they do.
Just keep her in the back of the line.
Roger that.
All right. listen up.
These photos were taken yesterday
at a safe house in Alpine.
Targets left five hours ago.
which should put them
at the San Antonio location
sometime in the next twenty minutes.
We do not know how
long they are held there
until their next leg. so
assuming they are on time this evening.
we hit the house at 0400.
Door locks are
electronic. gate code is 7358.
One four-man team enters from the front.
another one from the rear.
There are two beds in
each of the three bedrooms.
which leads us to believe two per room.
We're not going to have to guess
because we have video until we breech.
At that point. power will be
cut and overwatch will be blind.
Now. listen up. this is important.
This is a capture only mission.
That is not negotiable.
If for some reason this goes to shit.
they got a cache of
weapons and they are prepared.
so we fall back. we let
San Antonio SWAT take over.
Wait. wait. wait...
So you're saying if
we're fired upon we can't...
we can't return fire and save our ass?
I'm saying you lay suppressive fire
and pray to God you don't hit anybody.
What the fuck?
Let me walk you through
the gravity of the situation here.
We have one chance to give Border Patrol
and DPS a prize big enough
that they will look the
other way from the shit show
you created in Van Horn.
If this becomes a shit
show as well. there is no prize.
everyone runs for cover.
and you are all left
standing in the middle of the street
with your pants around your ankles.
Got it?
Border Patrol won't
lend us their Tactics team?
Eight on six doesn't make quick and quiet.
This is our mess. we clean it up.
You've got movement at the house.
Gun.
I see it.
That's fucking great.
They're armed.
Let me see if we can get some latitude.
Uh-oh.
Kaitlyn.
Are there any big sporting
events planned for tomorrow?
Why do you say tomorrow?
Would you set a bomb
beside your bed for a week?
When they arm them. they use them.
Actually. Bob. I'm gonna
need you to come down here.
Shit. This keeps going
from bad to fucking worse.
I hit a house like this in Pakistan.
But it was capture-kill.
And nobody was thinking capture.
You take it clean?
Guy in the back of the house detonated.
took three with him.
There was only one entrance though.
We just didn't have enough time.
Joe. Kyle.
Let's go.
We need to run this up the pole now.
We need Homeland Security.
you need to notify the Governor's office.
We are on a clock. and we
don't know when it runs out.
What are you gonna do.
have San Antonio SWAT
trying to take them on the street?
They'll blow up the
whole fucking neighborhood.
We have an HRT team in Houston.
That's too far.
We'd better decide something fast.
I need to evacuate the neighborhood.
Well. and how you plan to do that?
Gonna hit the civil service siren?
We have BP run it. take my team on loan.
This is clearly a threat.
We neutralize the threat.
FBI can withhold all evidence
because releasing would
jeopardize national security.
What about the medical examiner?
A bunch of soldiers
start neutralizing threats
while they're sleeping is
homicide any way you slice it.
You don't have the protection we have.
I have the answer. I just don't think
you want to be here when I say it.
Understood.
Yeah.
I'll step away.
Thank you.
You have engineers in San Antonio?
El Paso. I have a bomb unit in Laughlin.
I can have them here in three hours.
We neutralize the threat.
Close down the scene
until bomb squad has secured.
which they won't.
And then we evacuate the neighborhood
and detonate the bombs in place.
And with it...
Got it.
You up for playing
outside the lines tonight?
Your team better be pretty fucking special.
This is what we do.
Send 'em in.
Gear up.
You're green.
Yes. ma'am.
New deal. Weapons free.
We clear the scene.
When do we move?
Right now.
What about me?
What about you?
This I know.
Gear up.
When we reach the site. kill the power.
We don't want recordings of this shit.
When our boots hit
the ground. kill the power.
You got it.
What are you smiling about?
I haven't had this much fun since Iraq.
You're such an asshole. Kyle.
Yeah. but I'm good looking.
That makes it worse. you know that?
Fucking asshole. you can't even insult him.
All right. we're leaving in five.
Let's go.
Kyle. are you fucking wearing cologne?
I remember you now.
Baghdad. 2011.
Yep. I was there.
He wore that shit back then. too.
You stay right behind me.
You should stay behind me.
If you go into this trying to protect her.
you're going to get killed.
You go into this trying to prove yourself.
you're getting killed.
The only mission is the mission you're on.
Yes. ma'am.
Joe?
I hear you.
Joe.
Understood.
We're in position.
Power off.
Hallway right.
Going left.
On me.
Fuck.
Cruz. hold your position!
What the fuck are you doing?
Saving your life.
E.K.I.A. wearing suicide vest room 3.
Move off target.
Almost like we do this for a living.
This one activated his vest.
Even better.
Overwatch. this is QRF 2. house is secure.
One bandit activated IED.
Request bomb squad and engineers. over.
Copy. QRF 2. bomb squad is present.
Exit the house and they
will assume control of the scene.
One of them had a suicide vest.
It activated.
We've surrendered the
scene to the bomb squad.
I highly recommend you
evacuate the neighborhood.
it's likely they'll need to
blow the ordinance in place.
Well played. agent.
It's not a game. sir.
You don't smell like
cologne anymore. do you.
you rank motherfucker.
I think that's you.
Fuck you.
No. he's right.
It's you.
Good job.
What do I tell her?
Aaliyah.
It's been three days.
I don't know.
Tell her the truth.
Just leave out the names.
The truth?
The best lies are wrapped in it.
Let me get back to you.
Long one.
Not short.
If I guess where do I get a prize?
You'll never guess where.
San Antonio.
Border Patrol officials were compelled
to blow the explosives in place
destroying the house
where the terrorists were staying.
and with it any likely motive or target...
Little heads-up would have been nice.
You know what this has done to oil prices?
I want to invite our girls over for supper.
Bad week for it.
That wasn't a question.
I'm inviting our daughters over for dinner.
Don't make plans.
It's gonna happen again.
Where?
Don't know.
When?
Not sure.
Then how do you know?
They're coming in
through Mexico using the cartels
and we can't stop them.
And now the whole world knows.
I'm going to take a shower.
What did I miss?
Whole bunch of this.
Pain was pretty bad last
night. so upped her morphine.
Morphine?
Of the opioids
available it is the lesser of all evils.
Yeah. Yeah.
Trying to get this
damn thing set up for her.
Rough night?
Yeah.
Believe it or not. I've had worse.
Well that's terrifying.
Yeah.
Did ISIS come to Baltimore. Joe.
or am I married to a fucking hit man now?
NFL network replays games in the morning.
You are the perfect woman.
Fuck.
You hate me?
Why would I hate you?
I begged them to go
back for you. but the security
pushed us out.
FaceTime me.
Uh. no.
I look like hell.
That's not possible.
FaceTime me. Please.
Yeah. Yeah. just... give me two minutes.
Hey. Still in the Hamptons?
Where are you?
Dorm... Show me.
There's not much to see.
Show me anyway.
No. I'm embarrassed.
I don't have your money.
That's one of the things I like about you.
I want to see it. it's where you live.
Mm-mm. you're stuck looking at my face.
And what torture that is.
Fine. I'll look at your face.
We are lady and the tramp. you and I.
Except you are a lady. too.
so we are lady and the lady tramp.
Okay.
Weekdays here are the best.
New bathing suit.
For making the boys crazy.
Come back up.
No. I can't.
You can.
No. I don't like your friends.
They are gone.
I'm all alone.
Hey.